<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
	<idinfo>
		<citation>
			<citeinfo>
				<origin>Tele Atlas North America, Inc.</origin>
				<origin>ESRI</origin>
				<pubdate>20070501</pubdate>
				<title Sync="TRUE">AllCoBlocks</title>
				<edition>2007</edition>
				<geoform Sync="TRUE">vector digital data</geoform>
				<serinfo>
					<sername>ESRI® Data &amp; Maps</sername>
					<issue>2007 World, Europe, United States, Canada, and Mexico</issue>
				</serinfo>
				<pubinfo>
					<pubplace>Redlands, California, USA</pubplace>
					<publish>ESRI</publish>
				</pubinfo>
				<othercit>Location: \usa\census</othercit>
				<onlink></onlink>
				<ftname Sync="TRUE">AllCoBlocks</ftname></citeinfo>
		</citation>
		<descript>
			<abstract>U.S. Census Blocks represents the U.S. Census blocks of the United States.</abstract>
			<purpose>U.S. Census Blocks provides boundaries and demographic information for the U.S. Census blocks within United States. The boundaries are consistent with the tract, county, and state data sets.</purpose>
			<langdata Sync="TRUE">en</langdata></descript>
		<timeperd>
			<timeinfo>
				<mdattim>
					<sngdate>
						<caldate>200701</caldate>
					</sngdate>
					<sngdate>
						<caldate>20070606</caldate>
					</sngdate>
					<sngdate>
						<caldate>2000</caldate>
					</sngdate>
				</mdattim>
			</timeinfo>
			<current>publication date: 200701, 20070606; ground condition: 2000</current>
		</timeperd>
		<status>
			<progress>Complete</progress>
			<update>Annually</update>
		</status>
		<spdom>
			<bounding>
				<westbc>-178.227822</westbc>
				<eastbc>-65.244234</eastbc>
				<northbc>71.390482</northbc>
				<southbc>17.881242</southbc>
			</bounding>
			<lboundng><leftbc Sync="TRUE">1243799.282930</leftbc><rightbc Sync="TRUE">1428319.772090</rightbc><bottombc Sync="TRUE">321534.804500</bottombc><topbc Sync="TRUE">496995.233321</topbc></lboundng></spdom>
		<keywords>
			<theme>
				<themekt>None</themekt>
				<themekey>point</themekey>
				<themekey>census block groups</themekey>
				<themekey>demographics</themekey>
				<themekey>population</themekey>
				<themekey>households</themekey>
				<themekey>boundaries</themekey>
				<themekey>society</themekey>
			</theme>
			<place>
				<placekt>None</placekt>
				<placekey>United States</placekey>
			</place>
			<temporal>
				<tempkt>None</tempkt>
				<tempkey>2007</tempkey>
				<tempkey>2000</tempkey>
			</temporal>
		</keywords>
		<accconst>Access granted to Licensee only.</accconst>
		<useconst>The data are provided by multiple, third party data vendors under license to ESRI for inclusion on ESRI Data &amp; Maps for use with ESRI® software.  Each data vendor has its own data licensing policies and may grant varying redistribution rights to end users. Please consult the redistribution rights below for this data set provided on ESRI Data &amp; Maps. As used herein, ?Geodata? shall mean any digital data set consisting of geographic data coordinates and associated attributes.

The redistribution rights for this data set: Redistribution rights are granted by the data vendor for hard-copy renditions or static, electronic map images (e.g. .gif, .jpeg, etc.) that are plotted, printed, or publicly displayed with proper metadata and source/copyright attribution to the respective data vendor(s).  Geodata is redistributable with a Value-Added Software Application developed by ESRI Business Partners on a royalty-free basis with proper metadata and source/copyright attribution to the respective data vendor(s).

[Applicable to Department of Commerce, Census Bureau and ESRI sources only]?In addition to the redistribution rights above, geodata is redistributable without a Value-Added Software Application (i.e., adding the sample data to an existing, [non]commercial data set for redistribution) with proper metadata and source/copyright attribution to the respective data vendor(s).

The terms and conditions below apply to all the data sets provided on ESRI Data &amp; Maps.

Proprietary Rights and Copyright: Licensee acknowledges that the Data and Related Materials contain proprietary and confidential property of ESRI and its licensor(s). The Data and Related Materials are owned by ESRI and its licensor(s) and are protected by United States copyright laws and applicable international copyright treaties and/or conventions.

Limited Warranty and Disclaimer: ESRI warrants that the media upon which the Data and Related Materials are provided will be free from defects in materials and workmanship under normal use and service for a period of ninety (90) days from the date of receipt.

THE DATA AND RELATED MATERIALS ARE EXCLUDED FROM THE LIMITED WARRANTY, AND THE LICENSEE EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGES THAT THE DATA CONTAINS SOME NONCONFORMITIES, DEFECTS, OR ERRORS. ESRI DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE DATA WILL MEET LICENSEE'S NEEDS OR EXPECTATIONS; THAT THE USE OF THE DATA WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED; OR THAT ALL NONCONFORMITIES, DEFECTS, OR ERRORS CAN OR WILL BE CORRECTED. ESRI IS NOT INVITING RELIANCE ON THIS DATA, AND THE LICENSEE SHOULD ALWAYS VERIFY ACTUAL DATA.

EXCEPT FOR THE LIMITED WARRANTY SET FORTH ABOVE, THE DATA AND RELATED MATERIALS CONTAINED THEREIN ARE PROVIDED "AS-IS," WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.

HIGH RISK ACTIVITIES: 
(A) THE DATA AND RELATED MATERIALS ARE NOT FAULT-TOLERANT AND ARE NOT DESIGNED, MANUFACTURED, OR INTENDED FOR USE OR RESALE FOR INSURANCE UNDERWRITING OR WITH CRITICAL HEALTH AND SAFETY OR ONLINE CONTROL EQUIPMENT IN HAZARDOUS ENVIRONMENTS THAT REQUIRE FAIL-SAFE PERFORMANCE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE OPERATION OF NUCLEAR FACILITIES, NAVIGATION OR GUIDANCE (I.E., AIRCRAFT, NAUTICAL VEHICLE, ETC.), OR COMMUNICATION SYSTEMS, AIR TRAFFIC CONTROL, EMERGENCY RESPONSE, TERRORISM PREVENTION OR RESPONSE, LIFE SUPPORT, OR WEAPONS SYSTEMS ("HIGH RISK ACTIVITIES"). ESRI SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF FITNESS FOR HIGH RISK ACTIVITIES.

(B) TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, LICENSEE AGREES TO INDEMNIFY, DEFEND, AND HOLD ESRI, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUBCONTRACTORS, LICENSORS, SUCCESSORS, AND ASSIGNS HARMLESS FROM AND AGAINST ANY AND ALL LIABILITY, LOSSES, CLAIMS, EXPENSES (INCLUDING ATTORNEYS' FEES), DEMANDS, OR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH LICENSEE'S USE OR PERMITTING THE USE BY OTHERS OF THE DATA, AND VENDOR'S HARDWARE OR SOFTWARE FOR HIGH RISK ACTIVITIES. DELIVERY OF THE DATA, AND VENDOR'S HARDWARE OR SOFTWARE DOES NOT CONSTITUTE A WAIVER OF THE RIGHTS AND OBLIGATIONS SET FORTH IN THIS ARTICLE.

Exclusive Remedy and Limitation of Liability: The entire liability of ESRI or its licensor(s) and Licensee's exclusive remedy shall be to terminate the Agreement upon Licensee returning the Data and Related Materials to ESRI with a copy of Licensee's invoice/receipt and ESRI returning the license fees paid to Licensee.

IN NO EVENT SHALL ESRI AND/OR ITS LICENSOR(S) BE LIABLE FOR COSTS OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOST PROFITS, LOST SALES, OR BUSINESS EXPENDITURES, INVESTMENTS, OR COMMITMENTS IN CONNECTION WITH ANY BUSINESS; LOSS OF ANY GOODWILL; OR FOR ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THIS AGREEMENT OR USE OF THE DATA AND RELATED MATERIALS, HOWEVER CAUSED, ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, AND WHETHER OR NOT ESRI OR ITS LICENSOR(S) HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE. THESE LIMITATIONS SHALL APPLY NOTWITHSTANDING ANY FAILURE OF ESSENTIAL PURPOSE OF ANY EXCLUSIVE REMEDY.

Third Party Beneficiary: ESRI's licensor(s) has (have) authorized ESRI to (sub)distribute and (sub)license its (their) data as incorporated into the Data and Related Materials. As an intended third party beneficiary to this Agreement, the ESRI licensor(s) is (are) entitled to directly enforce, in its own name, the rights and obligations undertaken by the Licensee and to seek all legal and equitable remedies as are afforded to ESRI.

In the event that the data vendor(s) has (have) granted the end user permission to redistribute the Geodata, please use proper proprietary or copyright attribution for the various data vendor(s), and provide the associated metadata file(s) with the Geodata. In compliance with FGDC metadata standards, ESRI has attempted to practice proper metadata methodologies by providing any data source information, descriptions, and file names to assist in this effort.</useconst>
		<ptcontac>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>ESRI</cntorg>
					<cntper>Data Team</cntper>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype>
					<address>380 New York Street</address>
					<city>Redlands</city>
					<state>California</state>
					<postal>92373-8100</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>909-793-2853</cntvoice>
				<cntfax>909-793-5953</cntfax>
				<cntemail>info@esri.com</cntemail>
				<hours>7:00 a.m.5:30 p.m. Pacific time, MondayFriday</hours>
				<cntinst>
In the United States
Please direct all inquiries regarding software/data pricing and consulting services to your local ESRI Regional Office.  For support, you may contact Technical Support by telephone (voice) between 6:00 a.m. and 5:00 p.m. Pacific time, Monday through Friday, by dialing 888-377-4575; facsimile (fax) available at 909-792-0960; electronic mail (e-mail) support@esri.com; or visit http://support.esri.com; ESRI holidays excluded. 

Outside the United States
Please direct all inquiries regarding software/data pricing, sales, support, and consulting services to your local ESRI International Distributor.  This information can be found at http://gis.esri.com/intldist/contactint.cfm.  

For other questions or comments, you may contact ESRI headquarters by e-mail, telephone, or fax or write to us.
</cntinst>
			</cntinfo>
		</ptcontac>
		<native Sync="TRUE">Microsoft Windows XP Version 5.1 (Build 2600) Service Pack 2; ESRI ArcCatalog 9.3.0.1689</native>
		<natvform Sync="TRUE">Shapefile</natvform></idinfo>
	<dataqual>
		<logic>The shapefile is converted to SDC (Smart Data Compression) format using either ESRI SDC Data Development Kit Professional 2 (DDKP2) or tools in ArcGIS.  The SDC data set is then loaded into ArcSDE® to verify and validate the geometry.</logic>
		<complete>After processing, the data set is checked for drawing display and number of records and file sizes compared with source materials.</complete>
		<posacc>
			<horizpa>
				<horizpar>The geospatial part of this data set was extracted from the 2000 Census TIGER/Line® files. The positional accuracy of the TIGER/Line coordinates varies with the source materials used but at best meets the established National Map Accuracy standards (+/- 167 feet approximately) where 1:100,000-scale maps from the USGS are the source. The Census Bureau cannot specify the accuracy of feature updates added by its field staff or of features derived from the GBF/DIME-Files or other map sources. Thus, the level of positional accuracy in the TIGER/Line files is not suitable for high-precision measurement applications such as engineering problems, property transfers, or other uses that might require highly accurate measurements of the earth's surface.</horizpar>
			</horizpa>
		</posacc>
		<lineage>
			<srcinfo>
				<srccite>
					<citeinfo>
						<origin>Tele Atlas North America, Inc.</origin>
						<pubdate>200701</pubdate>
						<title>Dynamap/2000 v. 17.0</title>
						<edition>Version 17.0</edition>
						<geoform>vector digital data</geoform>
						<serinfo>
							<sername>Dynamap®/2000</sername>
							<issue>Version 17.0</issue>
						</serinfo>
						<pubinfo>
							<pubplace>Lebanon, New Hampshire, USA</pubplace>
							<publish>Tele Atlas North America, Inc.</publish>
						</pubinfo>
						<onlink>http://www.teleatlas.com/</onlink>
					</citeinfo>
				</srccite>
				<srcscale>100000</srcscale>
				<typesrc>DVD?ROM</typesrc>
				<srctime>
					<timeinfo>
						<sngdate>
							<caldate>200701</caldate>
						</sngdate>
					</timeinfo>
					<srccurr>publication date</srccurr>
				</srctime>
				<srccitea>Dynamap/2000 v. 17.0</srccitea>
				<srccontr>Attribute and geospatial data</srccontr>
			</srcinfo>
			<srcinfo>
				<srccite>
					<citeinfo>
						<origin>Department of Commerce, Census Bureau</origin>
						<pubdate>2001</pubdate>
						<title>Summary File 1 (SF1)</title>
						<edition>2000</edition>
						<serinfo>
							<sername>Summary File 1 (SF1)</sername>
							<issue>2000</issue>
						</serinfo>
						<pubinfo>
							<pubplace>USA</pubplace>
							<publish>Department of Commerce, Census Bureau</publish>
						</pubinfo>
						<othercit>The Summary File 1 (SF1) data is based on the 2000 Census of Population.</othercit>
					</citeinfo>
				</srccite>
				<typesrc>CDROM</typesrc>
				<srctime>
					<timeinfo>
						<sngdate>
							<caldate>2000</caldate>
						</sngdate>
					</timeinfo>
					<srccurr>ground condition</srccurr>
				</srctime>
				<srccitea>Census SF1</srccitea>
				<srccontr>Attribute data</srccontr>
			</srcinfo>
			<srcinfo>
				<srccite>
					<citeinfo>
						<origin>ESRI</origin>
						<pubdate>20070606</pubdate>
						<title>ESRI Community Data</title>
						<edition>2007</edition>
						<geoform>tabular digital data</geoform>
						<serinfo>
							<sername>ESRI® Community Data</sername>
							<issue>2007</issue>
						</serinfo>
						<pubinfo>
							<pubplace>Redlands, California, USA</pubplace>
							<publish>ESRI</publish>
						</pubinfo>
						<othercit>Provides the POP2007 attribute.</othercit>
						<onlink>http://www.esri.com</onlink>
					</citeinfo>
				</srccite>
				<typesrc>DVDROM</typesrc>
				<srctime>
					<timeinfo>
						<sngdate>
							<caldate>20070606</caldate>
						</sngdate>
					</timeinfo>
					<srccurr>publication date</srccurr>
				</srctime>
				<srccitea>ESRI Community Data</srccitea>
				<srccontr>Attribute data</srccontr>
			</srcinfo>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>The following steps were performed by ESRI: Extracted block group geography from Tele Atlas Dynamap/2000 v. 17.0.  Removed Alaskan islands west of 180 degrees longitude.  Created region features from the polygon features.  Attached and formatted the attributes from 2006 U.S. Census Block Groups.  Put "0" values into the attributes for the new features.  Put "-99" values into all number attributes (except SQMI) for Puerto Rico.  Replaced attribute POP2005 with POP2007 and attribute POP05_SQMI with POP07_SQMI.  Calculated new values for attributes POP00_SQMI, POP07_SQMI, and SQMI.  Converted the data set to SDC.  Created ArcGIS® layer file (.lyr), projection file (.prj), and spatial indices.</procdesc>
				<srcused>Dynamap/2000 v. 17.0</srcused>
				<srcused>Census SF1</srcused>
				<srcused>ESRI Community Data</srcused>
				<procdate>20070717</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Dataset copied.</procdesc>
				<srcused></srcused>
			</procstep>
			<procstep><procdesc Sync="TRUE">Metadata imported.</procdesc><srcused Sync="TRUE">C:\DOCUME~1\KRISTE~1\LOCALS~1\Temp\xml4C.tmp</srcused><date Sync="TRUE">20080512</date><time Sync="TRUE">17105300</time></procstep></lineage>
	</dataqual>
	<spdoinfo>
		<direct Sync="TRUE">Vector</direct>
		<ptvctinf>
			<sdtsterm Name="AllCoBlocks">
				<sdtstype Sync="TRUE">Entity point</sdtstype>
				<ptvctcnt Sync="TRUE">24283</ptvctcnt>
			</sdtsterm>
			<esriterm Name="AllCoBlocks"><efeatyp Sync="TRUE">Simple</efeatyp><efeageom Sync="TRUE">Point</efeageom><esritopo Sync="TRUE">FALSE</esritopo><efeacnt Sync="TRUE">24283</efeacnt><spindex Sync="TRUE">TRUE</spindex><linrefer Sync="TRUE">FALSE</linrefer></esriterm></ptvctinf>
	</spdoinfo>
	<spref>
		<horizsys>
			<geograph>
				<latres>0.000000</latres>
				<longres>0.000000</longres>
				<geogunit>Decimal degrees</geogunit>
			</geograph>
			<geodetic>
				<horizdn>D_WGS_1984</horizdn>
				<ellips>WGS_1984</ellips>
				<semiaxis>6378137.000000</semiaxis>
				<denflat>298.257224</denflat>
			</geodetic>
		</horizsys>
	</spref>
	<eainfo>
		<detailed Name="AllCoBlocks">
			<enttyp>
				<enttypl Sync="TRUE">AllCoBlocks</enttypl>
				<enttypds>Department of Commerce, Census Bureau</enttypds>
				<enttypt Sync="TRUE">Feature Class</enttypt><enttypc Sync="TRUE">24283</enttypc></enttyp>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>Shape</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Feature geometry.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>ESRI</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<udom>Coordinates defining the features.</udom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>FAMILIES</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>The number of families in 2000.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>Department of Commerce, Census Bureau</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<udom>Numbers for the features. All features for Puerto Rico have -99 values.</udom>
				</attrdomv>
			</attr>
			<attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">FID</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">FID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">8</attwidth><attrdef Sync="TRUE">Internal feature number.</attrdef><attrdefs Sync="TRUE">ESRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="TRUE">Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">ID</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">ID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">15</attwidth></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">STFID</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">STFID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">254</attwidth></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">STFID_1</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">STFID_1</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">6</atnumdec></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Tot</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Tot</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">6</atnumdec></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Male</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Male</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">6</atnumdec></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Male35T74</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Male35T74</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">6</atnumdec></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Fem</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Fem</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">6</atnumdec></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Fem35T74</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Fem35T74</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">6</atnumdec></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">MaleInc</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">MaleInc</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">6</atnumdec></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">FemInc</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">FemInc</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Float</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">13</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">11</atnumdec></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Inc</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Inc</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Float</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">11</atnumdec></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">X</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">X</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Float</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">11</atnumdec></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Y</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Y</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">6</atnumdec></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Families</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Families</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">6</atnumdec></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">FHHChld</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">FHHChld</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">18</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">6</attscale></attr></detailed>
	</eainfo>
	<distinfo>
		<distrib>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>ESRI; ESRI International Distributors</cntorg>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype>
					<address>380 New York Street</address>
					<city>Redlands</city>
					<state>California</state>
					<postal>92373-8100</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>800-447-9778</cntvoice>
				<cntinst>
In the United States, contact the ESRI Telebusiness staff at 800-447-9778 for more information about our software and data.

Outside the United States, please direct all inquiries to your local ESRI International Distributor.  This information can be found at http://gis.esri.com/intldist/contactint.cfm.
</cntinst>
			</cntinfo>
		</distrib>
		<resdesc>Offline Data</resdesc>
		<distliab>See use constraints.</distliab>
		<stdorder>
			<digform>
				<digtinfo>
					<formname>SDC</formname>
					<formspec>The SDC file contains the geospatial and attribute data. The SDI file contains the spatial index. The PRJ file contains the coordinate system information (optional). The XML file (*.sdc.xml) contains the metadata describing the data set (optional).</formspec>
					<filedec>ArcGIS® software</filedec>
					<transize>215.260</transize>
					<dssize Sync="TRUE">0.649</dssize></digtinfo>
				<digtopt>
					<offoptn>
						<offmedia>DVD?ROM</offmedia>
						<reccap>
							<recden>4.38</recden>
							<recdenu>GB (gigabytes)</recdenu>
						</reccap>
						<recfmt>UDF (Universal Disc Format)</recfmt>
					</offoptn>
				</digtopt>
			</digform>
			<fees>Software purchase price</fees>
			<ordering>ESRI Data &amp; Maps is available only as part of ESRI® software.</ordering>
		</stdorder>
		<techpreq>To use this data requires software that supports SDC files.</techpreq>
	</distinfo>
	<metainfo>
		<metd Sync="TRUE">20080512</metd>
		<metc>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>ESRI</cntorg>
					<cntper>Data Team</cntper>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype>
					<address>380 New York Street</address>
					<city>Redlands</city>
					<state>California</state>
					<postal>92373-8100</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>909-793-2853</cntvoice>
				<cntfax>909-793-5953</cntfax>
				<cntemail>info@esri.com</cntemail>
				<hours>7:00 a.m.5:30 p.m. Pacific time, MondayFriday</hours>
			</cntinfo>
		</metc>
		<metstdn Sync="TRUE">FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
		<metstdv Sync="TRUE">FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
		<mettc Sync="TRUE">local time</mettc>
		<metextns>
			<onlink>http://www.esri.com/metadata/esriprof80.html</onlink>
			<metprof>ESRI Metadata Profile</metprof>
		</metextns>
		<langmeta Sync="TRUE">en</langmeta><metextns><onlink Sync="TRUE">http://www.esri.com/metadata/esriprof80.html</onlink><metprof Sync="TRUE">ESRI Metadata Profile</metprof></metextns></metainfo>
	<Esri><CreaDate>20130127</CreaDate><CreaTime>12230300</CreaTime><SyncOnce>FALSE</SyncOnce><SyncDate>20080512</SyncDate><SyncTime>17105300</SyncTime><ModDate>20080512</ModDate><ModTime>17130100</ModTime><DataProperties><lineage><Process ToolSource="C:\Program Files\ArcGIS\Desktop9.4\ArcToolbox\Toolboxes\Data Management Tools.tbx\CopyFeatures" Date="20100118" Time="115713">CopyFeatures C:\ESRIPress\Gist1\SpatialAnalyst\AllCoBlocks.shp C:\ESRIPress\Gist1\SpatialAnalyst.gdb\AllCoBlocks # 0 0 0</Process><Process ToolSource="C:\Program Files\ArcGIS\Desktop9.4\ArcToolbox\Toolboxes\Data Management Tools.tbx\CalculateField" Date="20100131" Time="142451">CalculateField AllCoBlocks ZFHHChld ( [FHHChld] - 1.422147)/4.431302 VB #</Process><Process ToolSource="C:\Program Files\ArcGIS\Desktop9.4\ArcToolbox\Toolboxes\Data Management Tools.tbx\CalculateField" Date="20100202" Time="131931">CalculateField AllCoBlocks ZFHHChld ( [FHHChld] - 1.422147)/4.431302 VB #</Process><Process ToolSource="c:\program files\arcgis\desktop10.1\ArcToolbox\Toolboxes\Data Management Tools.tbx\CalculateField" Date="20120406" Time="153436">CalculateField AllCoBlocks ZFHHChld "([FHHChld] - 1.422147) / 4.431302" VB #</Process><Process ToolSource="c:\program files (x86)\arcgis\desktop10.1\ArcToolbox\Toolboxes\Data Management Tools.tbx\CalculateField" Date="20130127" Time="122936">CalculateField AllCoBlocks ZFHHChld ( [FHHChld]- 1.422147)/4.431302 VB #</Process></lineage></DataProperties><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat></Esri><dataIdInfo><envirDesc Sync="TRUE">Microsoft Windows XP Version 5.1 (Build 2600) Service Pack 2; ESRI ArcCatalog 9.3.0.1689</envirDesc><dataLang><languageCode Sync="TRUE" value="en"></languageCode></dataLang><idCitation><resTitle Sync="TRUE">AllCoBlocks</resTitle><presForm><PresFormCd Sync="TRUE" value="005"></PresFormCd></presForm></idCitation><spatRpType><SpatRepTypCd Sync="TRUE" value="001"></SpatRepTypCd></spatRpType><dataExt><geoEle><GeoBndBox esriExtentType="native"><westBL Sync="TRUE">1243799.28293</westBL><eastBL Sync="TRUE">1428319.77209</eastBL><northBL Sync="TRUE">496995.233321</northBL><southBL Sync="TRUE">321534.8045</southBL><exTypeCode Sync="TRUE">1</exTypeCode></GeoBndBox></geoEle></dataExt></dataIdInfo><mdLang><languageCode Sync="TRUE" value="en"></languageCode></mdLang><mdStanName Sync="TRUE">ISO 19115 Geographic Information - Metadata</mdStanName><mdStanVer Sync="TRUE">DIS_ESRI1.0</mdStanVer><mdChar><CharSetCd Sync="TRUE" value="004"></CharSetCd></mdChar><mdHrLv><ScopeCd Sync="TRUE" value="005"></ScopeCd></mdHrLv><mdHrLvName Sync="TRUE">dataset</mdHrLvName><distInfo><distributor><distorTran><onLineSrc><orDesc Sync="TRUE">002</orDesc><linkage Sync="TRUE">file://\\KURLANDVAIO2\C\Gistutorial\SpatialAnalyst\AllCoBlocks.shp</linkage><protocol Sync="TRUE">Local Area Network</protocol></onLineSrc><transSize Sync="TRUE">0.649</transSize></distorTran><distorFormat><formatName Sync="TRUE">Shapefile</formatName></distorFormat></distributor></distInfo><spatRepInfo><VectSpatRep><topLvl><TopoLevCd Sync="TRUE" value="001"></TopoLevCd></topLvl><geometObjs Name="AllCoBlocks"><geoObjTyp><GeoObjTypCd Sync="TRUE" value="004"></GeoObjTypCd></geoObjTyp><geoObjCnt Sync="TRUE">24283</geoObjCnt></geometObjs></VectSpatRep></spatRepInfo><mdDateSt Sync="TRUE">20080512</mdDateSt></metadata>
